What the horror!
Huh?
No, Jotro, Cutter, and Hermes
made it at the last second.
This game is over.
You don't have any more
allies to help you,
and you won't ever be
able to see the new moon.
That's where you're wrong, Emporio.
It appears that fate is
truly on my side and is
serving me with one less
test to prove my worthiness.
Do it, Hermes!
Pick up that gun, and take the shot!
Seamoon!
Stop time!
Start Platinum the World!
When time goes back to normal, that
spear will fly straight through you.
The spear missed its mark.
He moved slightly during the time stop.
It failed.
Poochie's still alive.
Yeah, and now this thing is
starting to float in the air, too!
The priest is taking shelter in the
goddamn displaced space shuttle!
Hey, you guys.
I don't think he's just
trying to get away.
It can't be.
Could he have discovered something
that's giving him the advantage?
Did he actually find the missing
element to complete his ability?
You were the ones who have been
helping to raise me up all along.
Ever since you were in prison, you
have been there, lending me aid.
Our Father who art in heaven, I
beseech you to lead and guide me.
I ask you to please watch over me, so
I may not walk down the wrong path.
It is to your very will that
I shall dedicate myself!
I can feel it!
The coordinates!
I'm here!
Let's go.
Hikari chin, Cameo ni Chaka.
Gettin' to!
Ikiru imi wo?
Seiko ni nokosu kana.
Heavens falling down!
Nozomi wo kudako.
Kong no kari no.
Destiny is mine!
Oso ne shite mo?
All of the future, as I can see,?
I will shine on the light of my life.
to those who share the
blood of the Drostars!
Look!
It's Anastasia!
He's already managed to get on the
outer wall of the space shuttle!
You're done for!
Now dive or drive!
My stand is Seamoon no longer.
The time for heaven has arrived at last.
It has completed!
The gravitational power is
coursing through my entire body!
Go to hell, you asshole!
Heaven doesn't need you!
Good afternoon, everyone.
The accident on State Highway
405 in Cape Canaveral,
with casualty numbers estimated
to be between 1 and 2,000,
was initially thought to
be caused by a collapse.
However,
since military vehicles have been
unable to approach the scene,
the situation seems to
be much more complicated.
More updates on this
story after the break.
This place is...
What the hell?
Anastasia!
Where did he go?
What's going on?
Are you worried about me, Jolene?
I'm glad you care it means a lot but more
importantly that damn priest got away.
He was engulfed in light
and then disappeared
we've gotta hurry and
find that space shuttle.
Right now we don't have
to look far it wasn't
the shuttle that moved i
think it was us it seems.
That we shifted about 200
meters away from it i have no
idea how but we were just behind
that building a moment ago.
Well i don't mean to be
rude Jotaro but i think
i'd remember if i were
blown away or whatever.
Yeah did no one else see
anything like that my
guess is that we were moved
by the reverse gravity.
Good theory but not
likely the gravitational
effect is already worn off
back there and besides.
The priest said that sea
moon was no longer his stand.
Charlene where is he can you sense which
way the priest is headed i can sense that
he's still here although that's about it
so we don't know where he's hiding or what
direction he's going only that he's around
and besides that he
definitely saw the spear
coming when star platinum sent it flying
towards his face even
while time was stopped.
In that split second he managed to dodge
because he could see but how'd he do it.
Wait i get it now the priest was all
like it's been completed and the time for
heaven has arrived and all that shit but
what if he was just feeding us a lie and
he was actually bluffing so he could buy
some time for himself and hide away until
the new moon tomorrow i say he's full of
it i bet he's just trying to get away.
Hermes i'd advise against going in that
building stay in an open area
the rain. The rain will soon pet.
We're soaked!
What's going on, you guys?
Hey, Hermes!
The hell are you doing?
Nah, it's this automatic door!
Shit!
It's fast!
What the hell, man?
Why does this thing
shut like a guillotine?
Already dry, but I was just soaking.
No, what the fuck is happening?
Be more careful, Hermes.
What?
It's time for the evening news.
We have continued reports on the Cape
Canaveral catastrophe on Highway 405.
Oh, uh, actually, my apologies.
We'll now be going to commercial.
Huh? What?
It's already over?
The sun's setting? Already?
Um, I'll have chocolate nuts and caramel
and strawberry chocolate chip and mint.
Oh, and orange vanilla, too, please.
Here.
That'll be six dollars.
Strike!
Oh, wow!
We've got one amazing rookie here, folks.
Looks like he's gonna be the MVP!
I guess I am amazing.
Huh?
I-It's hardened!
Ouch! That hurts! Help, Mommy!
Hey, Barry!
Go get 20 kilos of meat
from the freezer! Yes, sir.
Right away.
He finally hit it, but it's a puff-fly!
W-What happened?
He's bleeding from gusely!
It all happened in the blink of an eye!
Ah! Oh no!
The speed we're coming into
land with is way too high!
Yeah, but all the radios
seem to be normal.
This is bad! Pull off!
What was that?
The hell is going on?
Hermit!
I guess he wasn't bluffing after all.
I was wrong.
Turns out that bastard wasn't trying to
play a trick so he could get away from us.
And plus, there's my blood, even though
the wound is fresh and still bleeding.
It's already dried,
way faster than normal.
The blood's drying, instantly.
Jolene, the blood on your
face too, it's dried up.
And it looks like it's already
crumbling away. Yeah, true.
But what does that mean, and why?
It can't be.
Guys, he really was telling the truth.
The priest's new ability, he
already had it back on the shuttle!
And now everything is
moving at a faster speed.
Everything in this world is...
And I don't just mean the machines,
I'm talking literally everything!
Oh shit, the sun's already gone down,
and the stars are lighting up the sky!
Does that mean the
completion of his ability?
Seriously?
What the hell's going on here?
So then, this is what the
Priest's new ability can do?
Damn it!
The way the stars and clouds are moving,
they look like special
effects from a movie.
What exactly is this
new ability capable of?
That's not the only thing. It's time.
It's speeding up as well.
The passage of time is
going by faster and faster.
And under these circumstances,
it seems only he's safe.
Could he be the only one who can
withstand the rapid acceleration of time?
It's highly possible.
He was able to avoid the
spear I threw at him,
though it might have been unconsciously.
However, if he is capable of moving
under this rapid passing of time,
and if he's come to realize
that he can still move around...
Jolene, we're leaving.
We aren't safe here.
Staying out here any longer isn't wise.
No way!
Can you sense it as well?
Jolene, do you feel his presence?
Yeah, but where?
He keeps moving.
And the bastard's hiding himself.
So I can't tell where he's
at, but he's coming closer!
Not good.
Let's move.
Start running.
Now, everyone, get a move on.
Star Platinum, the world!
My time stopped.
It was drastically shortened. Ah, shit!
This way, Mr. Jotaro!
Thank you.
You're Anastasia, right?
Yes.
My stand is Diver Drive.
It can embed itself into anything.
Let's watch the other side.
Yeah, but the thing is so fast.
I don't think just being on
the lookout will do much.
By the way, Mr.
Jotaro,
I'm determined to protect your
daughter with everything I have.
We've already got ourselves caught
up in something we can't back out of,
but we will make it out alive.
So I'd like to ask you for your
blessing to marry your daughter.
Wait, what did you just say to me?
I asked you for your blessing. Please, Mr.
Jotaro, respectfully, I
want to marry your daughter.
I know now's not the best time, but all
you have to do is give me your permission.
If I may have her father's approval, it'd
mean more to me than you'll ever know.
I don't expect it to be easy,
and it's not like I've always felt
worthy enough to marry Jolene.
And sure, I have been branded a murderer,
so I'm well aware that there's no way Jolene
would fall in love with me right away.
But the sheer determination and pure
soul which Jolene inherited from you,
her father,
is the light that shines upon
the darkest part of my heart.
And it's that heart that
could collapse at any moment.
She is exactly what I need.
Just say yes.
Please, sir.
That word is all I need to hear.
I need you to let me marry her
when we make it out of this alive.
I don't know what you're
talking about are you insane?
look where we are
Anastasia
We need to stay together all of us.
Let's not scatter
Sure, we made it to this
roof and we're fine for now,
but there's no escape
Poochie still on the move.
I I've set up a barrier
around us with my strings,
but who knows if this will even work.
And since he was able
to complete his ability,
he's not just going to
let us get away scot-free.
No, he wants to see
this through to the end.
Because he knows that he's
going to have to kill us and
put an end to the Joestar
bloodline once and for all.
But still, we have no idea what he can do.
How the hell are we supposed
to fight against that?
Mr.
Jotaro, say yes!
Okay.
All of you, listen.
It may seem like we've been
cornered up here, but getting on
the roof was the right decision.
His new ability is to speed up
time, and he's the only person
who can move through it.
But it doesn't mean that
we can't see him at all.
According to the speed at which
the hands of my watch are moving,
the minute hand indicates that
it takes about two minutes
for a full hour to go by.
In other words,
someone running at ten
kilometers per hour would
seem to us as if they were
running at the same speed
as a bullet train.
However, we are still able to see
an approaching bullet train with our
naked eyes.
Stay calm and observe.
We can at least see his moves.
Try to sense where he's going next.
But that's so fast.
That means if a car is
going 60 kilometers per
hour it would feel like
1800 and a hundred will
be Mach 2.4 exactly but
Lucky for us the priest
is still reluctant to
climb up here and join us.
On this roof he's being
cautious because of me and my
ability to stop time for Several
seconds and there's still
something that none of us know
how will His ability evolve
from this point on I'm sure
the priest wants to learn his?
Stan's true worth.
Star Platinum! The world!
Where is he?
Where did that bastard go?
Something moves underneath that table.
He has to be around here somewhere.
The longest I can stop time
is five seconds at most.
I have to locate him and strike him down.
All in the span of five seconds.
Good grief. He's not there.
I must have been imagining
something moving down there.
That's the limit.
Now time will resume.
That's where he's hiding.
In a palm tree! What?
It can't be!
He's using it as a spring!
That's the limit!
Time will resume!
He's gonna launch himself off the tree!
He's there!
Oh, man!
Jolene! Behind you!
He's coming back!
Anastasia...
You just used your stand and dove
into my body at the last second.
In that moment, you let your stand
take the brunt of the attack,
so that I wouldn't have
to suffer a fatal wound.
But still.
It's still too short.
Stopping time for just
five seconds isn't enough.
And I'm not able to
stop time consecutively.
After I stop time for five
seconds using Star Platinum,
I have to take a moment
to catch my breath.
That's the only way that I
can stop time again so soon.
But now that the priest has
reached his full potential,
the only one who can
stand up to him is me.
When he's in close enough range, the
only chance I've got to take him out?
is right now while time is still stopped.
That's my limit.
Time will resume once again.
Oh no! Old man! Anastasia!
I suppose the one who will be first in
line to die will be Anastasia instead.
And not Jotaro.
But you know what?
Although it's something so vast
you will not be able to fathom it,
I will make this clear once and for all.
Time will keep racing by.
But for your clarification?
I did not obtain this ability just
so I could dispose of you all!
nor did I do it to
become the most powerful.
The true purpose of this
ability is to guide the
masses of humanity towards
everlasting happiness.
Allow me to introduce you to my
new stand, my gift to humanity.
I shall christen my stand.
Made in heaven!
is filled with hope of
some place other than here.
Although you think I smile
inside and all the while,
I'm wondering about my destiny!
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do
In my life?
I'm a dreamer
A distant dreamer
Dreaming far away!
From today
You Thank you.